After Sinbad conquered the dungeon,
many similar structures began to appear all over the world
And many came to challenge said dungeons.
It was the very start of the age of dungeon conquests.
Is this....
a dungeon?
I heard these dungeons were dangerous, but...
They're eating me?
Shit!
This is bad!
Not like this!
In that case...
I'll make sure to get out of here alive.
That door
I'm done running.
I'll become stronger!
Gotcha!
Dead already, huh?
Let me play a bit more, Vitel.
Sorry.
The guy from last night.
Wait. Don't approach it carelessly!
Shut up. Don't you order me around.
What's this?
The key to open that door.
Just ahead lies the treasure room.
Hey, you!
Give that back!
You were with Sinbad, right?
Where is he?
The key mine.
Huh?
Ignore him. Let's get to the treasure room.
Sinbad will come for sure. I'll keep the key safe.
Let's go. Don't bother with this weakling.
Wait!
I told you to wait!
What?
What are you doing?
T-This is the overpowering strength of the far north pillager tribe,
An Imuchakk's power.
The hell's his problem? What a pain in the ass.
Vittel, Mahad.
Go easy on him.
Who are these people? They have powers like this too?
Well, let's get started!
Take this!
This will be
your end!
Balalak Saika.
Shit.
That was a close one, Hina.
Sinbad...
Why?
Look at you getting all the way out here alone.
Long time no see, Sinbad.
Let's see... Who were you again?
I'd never forget a lady's name after seeing her once, but for guys...
You brat...
I see jokes still fly over your head as usual.
I knew we'd meet again
Drakon.
Greetings. I'm a Kou wizard advisor, Falan.
I'll make you feel misery.
Sinbad!
You are my prey!
Wait. This is no time to be killing each other.
Shut up. All I care about is killing you!
You still haven't learned, huh?
Hey, big boy!
We'll take you on.
Hey!
Got you!
Embrace your inner child once in a while, why don't ya?
How? How can you read my attacks?
Just 'cause.
I refuse to
lose to him!
I got you.
This is bad!
Vittel!
Baal!
That would be
a Dungeon item.
This time for sure... You're mine!
How about this?
Thalg Hajar!
The water is freezing?
How unspeakable.
Mustasim's magic research as well as their magicians are advancing.
But I'm not sure if they can use magic like this.
Just who is this wizard?
It seems they managed to escape.
However, you Sham Lash are not as great as I thought.
Huh? What did you say?
Am I wrong?
You can't even catch a boy and a some northerner by yourselves.
Drink this!
Huh?
What's that?
Magic tool made to heal wounds.
We can't let them get any further than us, after all.
My body feels lighter!
So what are we supposed to do now?
Be patient.
There's but one destination for those who enter dungeons.
That ice was amazing!
This time, I was saved by you.
Why did you come here?
Eh?
Why are you here?
It's because of you that I...
Baal!
Lend me your strength!
Crash down, Lightning!
I'll use this dungeon to get stronger!
Just what kind of strength are you looking for?
You're plenty strong.
This is the deepest part of the treasure room.
Well then. Inside we go.
It seems to be this.
Lord Dragl. Call the Djinn.
Yeah.
I am Valefor.
Who will be the king?
So he's this dungeon's Djinn.
It smells.
You. I know you're in a fake body.
It's just like the vile smell of that world's flower.
H-Hey!
Begone!
Falan turned into a doll?
What's wrong?
It seems the Djinn has a very sharp nose.
However, I have left them a  fun souvenir.
Lord Barbarossa.
Well, now it's just a matter of who will be the king.
It's me. I'll make a contract with you.
What will you do with the power of a king?
Naturally, I will take it back to Partevia
and use it to serve my king.
Eh? Seriously?
I'm kind of disappointed.
I put effort into it and everything.
What I asked is what you want to do with this power for yourself.
But with your answer, you're not fit to be a king.
We caught up to you, Drakon.
Sinbad.
Okay. Seems like all the survivors are gathered here now.
The one of you six to pass my test will be king.
The power of the king is almighty.
Power to destroy a country overnight, or the wealth to build one!
Well, who wants to become king?
With this power, one could mess around for the rest of their life.
By one of six, you mean I'm in this too?
Of course.
Everyone here has a chance, including you.
What does this mean?
I mean if you overcome this test you might find what you really want
and become molded into a king for all you know.
Is that supposed to make me happy?
However, this is my last chance.
Yo, thug, we'll be taking part of this for ourselves.
Escaping the organization never came across my mind
It's different if I have power.
Sounds good. I'll kill you all together.
It's a blood festival for everyone here!
I'm here to become stronger.
To become a powerful warrior renowned by everyone.
This time, with my own power.
Okay. I'll join too.
Si-Sinbad, you've already got--
You already have Baal, but you want me too?
How greedy.
Yes you're right.
I won't let you have it.
The power is mine, I won't let anyone else take it!
Same here.
This is good. Everyone has ambition filled eyes.
This will be you lot's final oponent.
A part of my soul, Minifor.
The final test is to catch this little one here.
Exactly what do you mean?
As I said, who first catches him will get the power of the king.
What?!
However, if no one can catch him before the last drop of this water clock,
You won't be able to leave the dungeon.
Very well. Let's begin.
Easy. This is all I have to do!
Well then, will he be caught?
He's mine!
Sorry, my aim seems to be off.
If it's come to that, I have an idea too.
Oh? And just what is that?
Good, keep going, mankind will never change.
Wait a minute.
Huh?
You guys need to calm down.
There's only one way to survive and that's to cooperate.
Screw that. Only one person can become king!
You think we're gonna work with each other?
And what if this is what Valefor wants?
It's hard to catch by yourself.
But, if we work together I'm sure we can do it.
But how do we actually catch him?
We surround Minifor
then jump at the same time.
After that we can just run after him.
If someone does catch him, no regrets.
Who will give the signal to start running?
The person giving the signal will have a huge disadvantage!
Then I will give the command.
What did you say?
Damn you.
That's why I won't join.
I have nothing to hold the feline djinn.
I already have one anyway.
Moreover, getting out of here alive is more important.
Do not rush! Note the distance between you and move in slowly!
We only have one chance!
I can't believe I'm following his plans.
But we have no other choice.
Hina, don't leave openings!
Something... Something's off.
I won't let anyone else have it!
I'll get it!
The power of a king.
He can't possibly have given up.
Is there really nothing more to this?
If so, I'll take it for myself!
Now!
It jumped?
Got ya!
My gut feeling was right!
Sinbad...
You tricked us!
You usurped me again!
I knew I should have killed you!
Is that so?
If I didn't do that, we would have never left the dungeon.
Or if I'd not told you to cooperate, we would never have left the dungeon.
Therefore, it is not about who is right or wrong.
But who should get the power of the king.
That's obviously me.
Why you ask?
I want this Djinn the most.
Can't sleep?
This is the path that Hina chose.
All we can do now is rely on Sinbad.
I ...
Will not die.
Yeah.
He had the most frightening eyes.
But ...
What would you use this power for?
To gain untold riches?
In order to have power beyond reason?
To conquer other countries?
If it were me, I'd use this power
To create a country that will change the world.
A country that can
change the world?
I've been thinking ever since I left Partevia,
as well as when I came here to Imuchakk.
I finally figured out what I should aim for
I want to unite the people and countries
and create a world where people go forward hand in hand.
That's why I want to create a country that joins the world together!
The world and present times are not that simple.
What you say can only exist in dreams!
That's why I'm doing it.
I, the young man who first conquered the first dungeon in history, Sinbad,
will establish a new nation to change the world!
What do you think?
Pretty exciting, eh?
I will definitely make it happen.
For some reason...
Sinbad's words are making me feel hot
His eyes were powerful and just pulled me in.
That's why I want you all to come with me, to create this new nation.
I want to follow him.
I need friends to help me.
Experts in business, clever diplomacy, smart information gathering, as well as...
those who can come along with my adventures through the world.
So this is a man fit to be king?
My dream is still far from being a reality.
Strength, friends, even myself. I want it all!
Therefore, I want you to join me by by side!
Hey, are you sure you want to be our allies?
Of course, I want to be allies with everyone here.
Looks like he'll accept people like us, eh, Mahad?
Excellent! I will also be your ally.
Thug?
Lately I've been bored in the organization.
Looking forward to working with you.
Yeah.
Stupid!
You think someone like me will be subordinated by you?
No.
I'll make you my ally!
What is this?
My body feels like it's burning. Who's inside me?
What's going on?
It has begun.
How dare you do this in my dungeon!
At this rate this monster will finish forming.
Blast that thing with Baal's power!
You're still a boy!
You don't understand.
Sinbad?
Wa-What are you doing?
I will not let any of my comrades be killed!